myschool.com.ng 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy Document | Myschool.com.ng

Effective: February, 2010 | Last Modified: April, 2011   
  
About myschool.com.ng

myschool.com.ng is an online information portal for aspirants, students, graduates and interested individual of variuous schools. Together with this, it allows our members to set up unique personal profiles that can be viewed by the world. Members of this online community can view each others' profiles, communicate with old friends and meet new friends on the service, share photos, post journals and comments, and describe their interests. To enrich our members' experience, we request and display some personal information to other members and visitors, which allows our users to identify each other. Members can change their profile information at any time and can control how other members and the service communicates with them.

myschool.com.ng cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, please email us at support@myschool.com.ng.

Information Collection and Use by myschool.com.ng   
myschool.com.ng collects user submitted information such as name, email address, Yahoo ID to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the myschool.com.ng service. myschool.com.ng also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, Date of birth, school address and department in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other.

myschool.com.ng also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes 

User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the myschool.com.ng social community. Email addresses are used communicate with one another and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of individual communication and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within myschool.com.ng or with each other through the myschool.com.ng service. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, myschool.com.ng allows users to search for other members using their usernames.

We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. It is important to note that the updates, newsletters or news will be that containing information about the individuals community only or improvement of any of or services (which the user has already paid for).

From time to time, myschool.com.ng or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on myschool.com.ng. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

Links   
myschool.com.ng contains links to sites. myschool.com.ng is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on myschool.com.ng. 

Journals, Message Boards, Polls, Classifieds and Public Forums  
Please be aware that whenever you voluntarily post public information to Journals, Message Boards, Classifieds or any other Public Forums that that information can be accessed by the public and can in turn be used by those people to send you unsolicited communications.  
  
Correcting/Updating or Removing Information   
myschool.com.ng users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as my controls. 

Third Party Advertising   
Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by myschool.com.ng or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by myschool.com.ng and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

Special Note About Google Advertising  
Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own [privacy policies](http://www.google.com/privacy.html). About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher's website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user's browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

Security   
myschool.com.ng member accounts are secured by member-created passwords. myschool.com.ng takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private by making the passwords encrypted so nobody can view them (not even the administrator). We use reasonable measures to protect other member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time For any additional information about the security measures we use on myschool.com.ng, please contact us a support@myschool.com.ng   
  
Sharing and Disclosure of Information myschool.com.ng Collects   
Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, myschool.com.ng will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary: (1) to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by myschool.com.ng, whether or not a response is required by applicable law; (2) to enforce the myschool.com.ng Terms of Use Agreement or to protect our rights; or (3) to protect the safety of members of the public and users of the service. myschool.com.ng reserves the right to transfer personal information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of myschool.com.ng or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest For more information see the "Changes in Our Privacy Policy" section below. 

Changes in Our Privacy Policy   
From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A User is bound by any minor changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days. 

Contacting the Web Site   
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at: support@myschool.com.ng or call: 08039201681
